<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="../assets/xml/rss.xsl" media="all"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Victor Pinto (Posts about python)</title><link>http://victorapinto.com/</link><description></description><atom:link href="http://victorapinto.com/categories/python.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><language>en</language><copyright>Contents © 2019 &lt;a href="mailto:victor.pinto@gmail.com"&gt;Victor Pinto&lt;/a&gt; </copyright><lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2019 23:20:12 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>Nikola (getnikola.com)</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Thoughts on my new website</title><link>http://victorapinto.com/posts/thoughts-on-my-new-website/</link><dc:creator>Victor Pinto</dc:creator><description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;I find creating websites a very difficult and time consuming task. Whether it was Microsoft Publisher (back in 1998), Geocities, HTML, PHP+HTML, Blogger, Wordpress or now a Static website generated in Nikola (Python based) I have always encountered the same problem. Designing is hard, creating content of quality and at a consistent pace is hard, and by the time I get proficient with a particular technology or programming language, it's already obsolete. I have still try them all, created countless websites for courses I taught, shared a fair share of nonsense in blogs, and maintained a few mid-sized projects with different degrees of success.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So, why am I trying again? The main reason is that I realized that after so many years of education, research and experience, I'm still really bad at telling people the things I do and why they are (sometimes) important. In part, this is because I never feel very secure in my knowledge and I hate when I communicate ideas that are incorrect, but also because I have never mastered the art of communicating in English (which is not my native language).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I feel that I need to practice writing in English beyond the scientific writing I do from time to time to publish a paper, so here I am.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I'm thankful that I was able to find a static website generator that allows me to showcase my skills at running code in Python (because I'm not really programming a lot to publish this) and to not have to worry about the website design. Plus, It'll force me to learn Markdown.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><category>nikola</category><category>python</category><category>static</category><category>website</category><guid>http://victorapinto.com/posts/thoughts-on-my-new-website/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 18:35:01 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>